<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Spelling Techniques on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/spelling-techniques/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spelling Techniques on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/spelling-techniques/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe the Surprising Way to Spell &#39;Rock&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-surprising-way-to-spell-rock-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-surprising-way-to-spell-rock-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever been surprised by the English language? From the silent letters in words like “psychology” to the seemingly random spelling of words like “colonel”, the English language is full of surprises. Today, we’re going to look at one of those surprises: the surprising way to spell the word “rock”.
The Surprising Way to Spell ‘Rock’ You’ve probably seen the word “rock” spelled in a variety of ways: “rok”, “roc”, and “roque”, to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know the Astonishingly Simple Way to Spell Chrome?</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-astonishingly-simple-way-to-spell-chrome-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-astonishingly-simple-way-to-spell-chrome-/</guid>
      <description>The Astonishingly Simple Way to Spell Chrome Chrome is a web browser developed by Google and is one of the most popular browsers in the world. It is used by millions of people every day and is a key component of the modern internet experience.
However, many people have trouble spelling Chrome correctly. This is because there are several different ways to spell it, and it can be difficult to remember which one is correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know the Astonishingly Simple Way to Spell Cherokee?</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-astonishingly-simple-way-to-spell-cherokee-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-astonishingly-simple-way-to-spell-cherokee-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the Cherokee Language The Cherokee language is an ancient language spoken by the Cherokee people, who are indigenous to the southeastern United States. It is a polysynthetic language, meaning that it has many words that are made up of multiple parts. The Cherokee language is one of the few indigenous languages still spoken in the United States.
How to Spell Cherokee Learning to spell Cherokee can seem like a daunting task, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
