<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make You Understand &#39;How You Like That&#39; Meaning in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-understand-how-you-like-that-meaning-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-understand-how-you-like-that-meaning-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever heard the phrase &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; and wondered what it meant? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! This phrase has become popular in recent years and many people are curious about its meaning. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; means, how it can be used, and how you can quickly understand its meaning.
What “How You Like That” Means The phrase &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; is a way of asking someone what they think about something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Listen to The Fray&#39;s &#39;How To Save A Life&#39; CD!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-listen-to-the-fray-s-how-to-save-a-life-cd-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-listen-to-the-fray-s-how-to-save-a-life-cd-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You Listen to The Fray&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;How To Save A Life&amp;rsquo; CD! Music has the power to move us in many ways, and the music of The Fray is no exception. Their 2006 album, &amp;lsquo;How To Save A Life&amp;rsquo;, is a perfect example of how music can have a lasting impact on our lives.
A. Background of The Fray The Fray is a four-piece rock band from Denver, Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Hear This Song - You&#39;ll Be Hooked Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-hear-this-song-you-ll-be-hooked-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-hear-this-song-you-ll-be-hooked-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever heard a song that you just can&amp;rsquo;t get out of your head? That&amp;rsquo;s what we call a &amp;ldquo;hook&amp;rdquo; song. Hook songs are incredibly catchy and have the power to instantly captivate even the most passive of listeners. Listening to a hook song can be beneficial in a number of ways, from providing a fun distraction to helping you stay focused on a task. We recently stumbled upon a song that has all the makings of a classic hook song, and today we&amp;rsquo;re sharing it with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Woolf Shows You How to Change Lives Forever with His Cover of &#39;How to Save a Life&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/sam-woolf-shows-you-how-to-change-lives-forever-with-his-cover-of-how-to-save-a-life-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/sam-woolf-shows-you-how-to-change-lives-forever-with-his-cover-of-how-to-save-a-life-/</guid>
      <description>on the Audience
Introduction Sam Woolf is a singer-songwriter from Florida who has gained international recognition for his powerful and emotive covers of popular songs. His cover of the song &amp;ldquo;How to Save a Life&amp;rdquo; by The Fray is particularly noteworthy for its ability to touch the hearts of listeners and to inspire them to make a difference in the world. In this blog post, we will take a look at the background of Sam Woolf, the lyrical and musical elements of his cover, and the impact that it has had on his audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Hear BLACKPINK&#39;s New Song &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-hear-blackpink-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-hear-blackpink-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction BLACKPINK is a South Korean girl group that debuted in 2016. The group consists of four members, Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa, and is managed by YG Entertainment. BLACKPINK is one of the most popular K-pop groups in the world and has achieved incredible success, with their songs topping the charts all over the world. Recently, the group released their new single, &amp;ldquo;How You Like That,&amp;rdquo; and it has been met with an overwhelmingly positive response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Change the Way You Look at &#39;Fray How To Save A Life&#39; Forever!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-change-the-way-you-look-at-fray-how-to-save-a-life-forever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-change-the-way-you-look-at-fray-how-to-save-a-life-forever-/</guid>
      <description>This One Simple Trick Will Change the Way You Look at &amp;lsquo;Fray How To Save A Life&amp;rsquo; Forever! We all know the song &amp;lsquo;Fray How To Save A Life&amp;rsquo; by The Fray. It&amp;rsquo;s an emotionally charged song with a powerful message. But what does it really mean? In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the deeper meaning of the song and explore how it can help us better understand our own lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Much Blackpink&#39;s &#39;How You Like That&#39; Sold in Its First Week!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-much-blackpink-s-how-you-like-that-sold-in-its-first-week-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-much-blackpink-s-how-you-like-that-sold-in-its-first-week-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is one of the most popular K-Pop girl groups in the world, and their latest single &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; has been an absolute smash hit. In its first week of release, the single sold an incredible amount of copies, and it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to Blackpink&amp;rsquo;s incredible success and popularity. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the sales of &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; in its first week, and how it compares to other artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Listen To BLACKPINK&#39;s &#39;How You Like That&#39; On Spotify!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-listen-to-blackpink-s-how-you-like-that-on-spotify-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-listen-to-blackpink-s-how-you-like-that-on-spotify-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a fan of K-Pop? Then you must know BLACKPINK! This South Korean girl group is one of the biggest names in the industry, and they have just released their single &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; on Spotify. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard it yet, you won&amp;rsquo;t believe what happens when you listen to it!
Overview of BLACKPINK and their song How You Like That BLACKPINK is a four-member girl group that debuted in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grandeCan You Believe This? Find Out How to Spell Ariana Grande&#39;s Name Right Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/grandecan-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-ariana-grande-s-name-right-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/grandecan-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-ariana-grande-s-name-right-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ariana Grande is one of the most popular singers and songwriters of the 21st century. From her hit singles to her award-winning albums, Ariana has made a name for herself in the music industry. But there&amp;rsquo;s one thing that has always stumped fans and casual listeners alike: how to spell Ariana Grande&amp;rsquo;s name correctly.
Overview of Ariana Grande Ariana Grande-Butera was born on June 26, 13 in Boca Raton, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Just Did - Get Ready to Be Blown Away!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-get-ready-to-be-blown-away-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-get-ready-to-be-blown-away-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is a South Korean girl group that has taken the world by storm since their debut in 2016. They have become one of the most popular K-pop groups in the world and have achieved immense success in the music industry. Recently, they made a surprise announcement that has left their fans in awe. Read on to find out what they did and why it has made such a big impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Just Did - You&#39;ll Love It!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-you-ll-love-it-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-you-ll-love-it-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is one of the most popular K-pop girl groups in the world. Their music, fashion, and style have been embraced by millions of fans around the world. Recently, Blackpink did something that has taken the world by storm. Read on to learn more about what Blackpink just did and the impact it has had.
Overview of Blackpink Blackpink is a four-member girl group from South Korea. The group consists of members Jisoo, Jennie, Lisa, and Rosé.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Poster Just Dropped the Hottest Song of the Summer - You Won&#39;t Believe What She Did Next!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/lisa-poster-just-dropped-the-hottest-song-of-the-summer-you-won-t-believe-what-she-did-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/lisa-poster-just-dropped-the-hottest-song-of-the-summer-you-won-t-believe-what-she-did-next-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This summer, Lisa Poster has taken the music world by storm with her latest single, &amp;ldquo;Can&amp;rsquo;t Stop Now&amp;rdquo;. Not only is the song an instant hit, but Lisa has been taking bold steps to ensure that her music reaches as many people as possible. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the background of Lisa Poster, the reaction to her new song, and what she&amp;rsquo;s been up to since its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What BLACKPINK Just Did With Their New Single &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-with-their-new-single-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-with-their-new-single-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What BLACKPINK Just Did With Their New Single &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo;! BLACKPINK is one of the most popular K-pop girl groups in the world, and they just achieved something incredible with their new single, &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo;. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the background of BLACKPINK, the impact of &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo;, and what this means for the group&amp;rsquo;s future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackpink Rose Just Blew Our Minds Away With Her New Single &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/blackpink-rose-just-blew-our-minds-away-with-her-new-single-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/blackpink-rose-just-blew-our-minds-away-with-her-new-single-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink Rose has just released her new single, &amp;ldquo;How You Like That,&amp;rdquo; and it has already made a huge impact on the music industry. Rose is a South Korean singer, songwriter, and rapper who is a member of the K-pop girl group Blackpink. She made her solo debut with the single &amp;ldquo;Gone&amp;rdquo; in March 2020, and has since become one of the most popular solo female artists in K-pop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rose of Blackpink Will Blow Your Mind with Her 2020 Comeback: How You Like That!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/rose-of-blackpink-will-blow-your-mind-with-her-2020-comeback-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/rose-of-blackpink-will-blow-your-mind-with-her-2020-comeback-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Rose of Blackpink is a South Korean singer and dancer who has been making waves in the K-Pop industry since her debut in 2016. With her powerful vocals and energetic stage presence, Rose has become one of the most popular members of the girl group Blackpink. In 2020, Rose made her solo debut with the single “How You Like That”, which took the world by storm and cemented her status as a global star.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When She Heard That Song - That How You Like That!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-heard-that-song-that-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-heard-that-song-that-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Music has the power to bring us joy, sorrow, and everything in between. It can take us back in time and make us feel things we never thought we could. Today, we’re going to talk about one woman’s reaction to a song that changed her life.
Background Information The song in question is “How You Like That” by the K-pop group BLACKPINK. This song was released in 2020 and quickly became a worldwide hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Lisa From Blackpink Just Did In This Photo!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-lisa-from-blackpink-just-did-in-this-photo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-lisa-from-blackpink-just-did-in-this-photo-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lisa from Blackpink is one of the most popular K-pop idols in the world. She is known for her amazing dancing and singing skills, as well as her amazing fashion sense. Recently, Lisa posted a photo of herself on her Instagram account that has caused quite the stir among her fans. In the photo, Lisa is seen wearing a white dress and posing in a way that has left many of her fans in awe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
