<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Much 100 Yen Is Worth! Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-much-100-yen-is-worth-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-much-100-yen-is-worth-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered how much 100 Yen is worth? 100 Yen is Japan&amp;rsquo;s currency and it can be used to purchase a variety of goods and services. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the value of 100 Yen, its history, and what you can buy with it.
Overview of 100 Yen 100 Yen is the basic unit of Japan&amp;rsquo;s currency. It is equal to about 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Airplane Fly Farther Than You Ever Imagined!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-imagined-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-imagined-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to make your airplane fly farther than ever before? Well, look no further! This simple trick is sure to make your airplane fly farther than you ever imagined.
Definition of the Trick The trick is to use the Bernoulli Principle to reduce drag and increase lift. The Bernoulli Principle states that when air is forced to move faster, it creates a decrease in pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Plane Fly Further Than You Ever Thought Possible!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-plane-fly-further-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-plane-fly-further-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Traveling by plane can be a great way to get from point A to point B, but sometimes it can be expensive. Fortunately, there is a simple trick that can help you get more out of your plane ride and save money. In this blog post, we will explain this trick and provide you with steps to implement it.
Overview of the Trick The trick is to increase the efficiency of your plane&amp;rsquo;s engines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Plane Fly Better Than Ever Before!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-plane-fly-better-than-ever-before-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-plane-fly-better-than-ever-before-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever feel like your plane isn&amp;rsquo;t performing as well as it should? Are you looking for a way to improve its performance and reduce fuel consumption? If so, this simple trick will help you get the most out of your plane.
Background Information The trick involves a simple modification to the way your plane is flown. By making a few small changes to the way you fly, you can significantly improve your plane&amp;rsquo;s performance and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Flying Delta Paper Airplanes in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-flying-delta-paper-airplanes-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-flying-delta-paper-airplanes-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to make and fly your own paper airplane? If so, then you’re in luck! Delta paper airplanes are an easy and fun way to get your feet off the ground. In this blog post, we’ll discuss what a delta paper airplane is, the benefits of flying them, and the steps to making one.
Definition of a Delta Paper Airplane A delta paper airplane is a type of paper airplane that is designed to fly long distances.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
