<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Surprise on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/surprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Surprise on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/surprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When We Asked &#39;How You Like That?&#39;</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-asked-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-asked-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever asked someone how they like something, only to get a response that you weren&amp;rsquo;t expecting? We recently did just that and the results were surprising. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take you through the process of asking the question, the responses we received, and our analysis of the responses.
Background Information Asking someone how they like something can be a tricky business. Depending on the person and the situation, the response can range from a polite &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s alright&amp;rdquo; to an enthusiastic &amp;ldquo;I love it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What You Need to Know Before You Spell &#39;Balance&#39; - It Might Surprise You!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/what-you-need-to-know-before-you-spell-balance-it-might-surprise-you-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/what-you-need-to-know-before-you-spell-balance-it-might-surprise-you-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When it comes to spelling words, balance is one of the most commonly misspelled words. It can be difficult to remember how to spell balance correctly, especially when there are so many other words that sound similar. But, with a little bit of practice and understanding, you can learn how to spell balance correctly. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss what balance is, why it is important to know how to spell it correctly, and the steps you can take to ensure that you spell it correctly every time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When She Gave Him That Rose!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-gave-him-that-rose-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-gave-him-that-rose-/</guid>
      <description>I. Introduction We all know the old saying, &amp;ldquo;A rose by any other name would smell as sweet,&amp;rdquo; but what happens when you give a rose to someone special? This story will show you just how powerful a single rose can be.
II. What Happened? Once upon a time, there was a young man who had been in love with a woman for years. He had never been able to find the courage to tell her how he felt, so he decided to give her a rose as a token of his love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When She Saw That Poster!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-saw-that-poster-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-saw-that-poster-/</guid>
      <description>I. Introduction It was a beautiful sunny day and she was out for a walk. She had no idea what was about to happen when she stumbled upon a poster that changed her life forever.
II. The Poster When she saw the poster, she was immediately intrigued. It was a colorful ad for a new product that promised to make life easier. She was so excited that she decided to buy it right away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
