<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Paper Art on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/paper-art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paper Art on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/paper-art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make Paper Jets!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-paper-jets-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-paper-jets-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make Paper Jets! Making paper jets is a fun, simple activity that anyone can do. With just a few materials, you can make a paper jet that will fly! Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to making paper jets that you and your family can enjoy.
Introduction Making paper jets is a great way to have fun and spend quality time with your family. Not only is it a fun activity, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to teach children about science and aerodynamics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is to Create an Amazing Airplane Out of Just Paper!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-create-an-amazing-airplane-out-of-just-paper-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-create-an-amazing-airplane-out-of-just-paper-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to make your own airplane out of paper? It may seem like an impossible task, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually surprisingly easy! With just a few simple materials and some patience, you can create an amazing paper airplane that will be the envy of your friends.
Overview of the Project Creating a paper airplane is a great way to have fun and learn something new. It&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to practice your origami skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make a Paper Fighter Jet -- Here&#39;s How!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-a-paper-fighter-jet-here-s-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-a-paper-fighter-jet-here-s-how-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make a Paper Fighter Jet &amp;ndash; Here&amp;rsquo;s How! Are you looking for a fun and creative way to spend your time? Why not make your very own paper fighter jet? It&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think!
I. Introduction A paper fighter jet is a model airplane made out of paper that looks like a real fighter jet. It can be used for decoration or as a toy for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Amazing Trick to Make an Airplane Out of Paper!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-amazing-trick-to-make-an-airplane-out-of-paper-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-amazing-trick-to-make-an-airplane-out-of-paper-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and creative way to pass the time? Have you ever wanted to make your own airplane out of paper? Well, now you can with this amazing trick!
Overview of the Trick This easy-to-follow trick will show you how to make an airplane out of paper. You will need some basic materials like paper, scissors, and glue. With a few simple steps, you will be able to make your own paper airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Create a Paper Jet Fighter in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-create-a-paper-jet-fighter-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-create-a-paper-jet-fighter-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Making a paper jet fighter is a fun and easy way to pass the time. It&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to teach children the basics of paper folding and origami. With just a few simple materials and a few easy steps, you can make your own paper jet fighter in no time!
Definition of a Paper Jet Fighter A paper jet fighter is a paper craft that is made by folding paper into a triangle shape and then cutting out a jet design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
