<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Language Learning on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/language-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Language Learning on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/language-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Master the Spelling of &#39;Gecko&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-master-the-spelling-of-gecko-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-master-the-spelling-of-gecko-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Gecko Gecko is a species of small lizard found in many parts of the world. They are known for their vibrant colors and unique abilities, such as their ability to stick to surfaces and climb walls. While they may be small and seemingly harmless, geckos can be quite tricky to spell correctly. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;ve come up with this one simple trick to help you master the spelling of &amp;lsquo;gecko&amp;rsquo;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Out Now: The Surprising Way to Spell &#39;Status&#39; That Everyone is Talking About!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/find-out-now-the-surprising-way-to-spell-status-that-everyone-is-talking-about-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/find-out-now-the-surprising-way-to-spell-status-that-everyone-is-talking-about-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered why the word “status” is spelled the way it is? It turns out that there is a surprising new way to spell this word that everyone is talking about. In this blog post, we’ll discuss the definition of “status”, the surprising way to spell it, and the impact this could have on language and communication.
Definition of “status” The word “status” is defined as “the relative importance, standing, or position of a person or thing in relation to others”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Master the Spelling of &#39;Continued&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-master-the-spelling-of-continued-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-master-the-spelling-of-continued-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you having trouble remembering how to spell the word “continued”? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. It&amp;rsquo;s a tricky word, and one that many English learners struggle with. But don&amp;rsquo;t worry – there&amp;rsquo;s a simple trick that can help you master the spelling of this word in no time.
Definition of “Continued” Before we get into the trick, let&amp;rsquo;s take a quick look at the definition of “continued”. This word is an adjective that means “continuing or extending without interruption or intervening period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This ONE Simple Trick Will Help You Master the Spellling of &#39;Legitimate&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-master-the-spellling-of-legitimate-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-master-the-spellling-of-legitimate-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever find yourself struggling to spell the word &amp;rsquo;legitimate&amp;rsquo;? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss why mastering the spelling of &amp;rsquo;legitimate&amp;rsquo; is important, as well as provide a few simple steps to help you master it.
What is Legitimate? The word &amp;rsquo;legitimate&amp;rsquo; is an adjective that means &amp;ldquo;in accordance with the law or established rules&amp;rdquo;. It can also be used to describe something that is accepted as true or accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
