<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Origami on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/origami/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Origami on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/origami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Making Paper Airplanes that Can Carry Coins in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-making-paper-airplanes-that-can-carry-coins-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-making-paper-airplanes-that-can-carry-coins-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and easy way to make something amazing? Look no further! With this simple trick, you can learn how to make paper airplanes that can carry coins.
Definition of Paper Airplanes A paper airplane is a small paper craft that is folded and then launched by hand. It is a form of aerodynamic transport that relies on the thrust created by throwing the paper craft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make The Perfect Paper Airplane Origami!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-the-perfect-paper-airplane-origami-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-the-perfect-paper-airplane-origami-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper airplane origami is a fun and creative way to make a paper airplane. Origami is the art of folding paper into intricate shapes and designs, and paper airplane origami is no different. It can be used to make a variety of different paper airplanes, from simple to complex. In this blog post, we’ll discuss what paper airplane origami is, the benefits of creating paper airplane origami, and how to make the perfect paper airplane origami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Change the Way You Fold Airplane Paper Forever!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-change-the-way-you-fold-airplane-paper-forever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-change-the-way-you-fold-airplane-paper-forever-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you remember the days of childhood when you would pass the time by folding paper airplanes? If you’ve ever wanted to revisit that fun activity, then this post is for you! In this post, we will be discussing a simple trick that will change the way you fold airplane paper forever.
Overview of the Trick The trick we will be discussing is a method for folding airplane paper that is easy to learn and produces beautiful, intricate designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Amazing Trick Will Have You Flying High - Learn How to Make an Origami Aeroplane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-amazing-trick-will-have-you-flying-high-learn-how-to-make-an-origami-aeroplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-amazing-trick-will-have-you-flying-high-learn-how-to-make-an-origami-aeroplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the Amazing Trick of Making an Origami Aeroplane Origami is the ancient art of paper folding. It has been used for centuries to create a variety of shapes and objects. Origami is a fun and creative way to express yourself.
A. Definition of Origami
Origami is the Japanese art of folding paper into intricate designs, such as animals, flowers, and other shapes. The word origami comes from two Japanese words: ori (to fold) and kami (paper).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make You a Master of Origami Airplane-Making in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-a-master-of-origami-airplane-making-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-a-master-of-origami-airplane-making-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Making origami airplanes is a fun and creative activity that can be enjoyed by people of all ages. With just a few simple supplies and a bit of practice, anyone can become a master of origami airplane-making in no time. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the benefits of learning this simple trick and provide a step-by-step guide to help you get started.
Overview of Origami Airplane-Making Origami is the Japanese art of paper folding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Teach You How to Make an Airplane Origami in Just Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-make-an-airplane-origami-in-just-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-make-an-airplane-origami-in-just-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Origami Origami is the art of folding paper into beautiful and intricate shapes. Origami is a Japanese word that literally translates to &amp;ldquo;folding paper&amp;rdquo;. It is a fun and creative activity that can be enjoyed by people of all ages.
Benefits of Origami Origami is a great way to relax and destress. It takes concentration and focus to create the intricate designs, which can help to clear the mind and reduce stress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Trick to Make an Origami Paper Airplane in Just Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-to-make-an-origami-paper-airplane-in-just-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/astonishing-trick-to-make-an-origami-paper-airplane-in-just-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Origami is a traditional Japanese art form that involves folding paper into intricate shapes and figures. It is an enjoyable activity for both children and adults alike, and it is a great way to pass the time and practice your creativity. In this article, we will be discussing an astonishing trick to make an origami paper airplane in just minutes!
Definition of Origami Origami is a type of art form that involves folding paper into a variety of shapes and figures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
