<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Entertainment on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/entertainment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entertainment on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/entertainment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Old Rapper Dream Is Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-old-rapper-dream-is-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-old-rapper-dream-is-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Dream is one of the most successful rappers of the 21st century. From his breakthrough single Throw It Back to his successful debut album It&amp;rsquo;s About Time, Dream has made a name for himself in the rap game. But what many people don&amp;rsquo;t know is that Dream is actually much older than what you would expect. Read on to learn more about Dream&amp;rsquo;s career and current life.
Overview of Dream&amp;rsquo;s Career Dream began his career in the early 2000s with his breakout single Throw It Back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Believe This? Find Out How to Spell Pinocchio in Just 5 Seconds!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-pinocchio-in-just-5-seconds-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-pinocchio-in-just-5-seconds-/</guid>
      <description>Can You Believe This? Find Out How to Spell Pinocchio in Just 5 Seconds! We all know the classic story of Pinocchio, the wooden puppet who wants to become a real boy. But do you know how to spell Pinocchio? If not, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll teach you how to spell Pinocchio in just seconds.
I. Introduction A. Definition of Pinocchio
Pinocchio is a fictional character created by Italian author Carlo Collodi in 1883.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can&#39;t Believe How Many People Get This Justin Bieber Spelling Question Wrong!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-t-believe-how-many-people-get-this-justin-bieber-spelling-question-wrong-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-t-believe-how-many-people-get-this-justin-bieber-spelling-question-wrong-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that so many people get a Justin Bieber spelling question wrong! For those unfamiliar with Justin Bieber, he is a Canadian pop singer and songwriter who has had a successful career in the music industry since his debut in 2009. His music has been popular with people of all ages and his fan base is massive. Despite his popularity, many people still struggle to spell his name correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Hear BLACKPINK&#39;s New Song &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-hear-blackpink-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-hear-blackpink-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction BLACKPINK is a South Korean girl group that debuted in 2016. The group consists of four members, Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa, and is managed by YG Entertainment. BLACKPINK is one of the most popular K-pop groups in the world and has achieved incredible success, with their songs topping the charts all over the world. Recently, the group released their new single, &amp;ldquo;How You Like That,&amp;rdquo; and it has been met with an overwhelmingly positive response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Incredible Paper Airplane Trick!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-paper-airplane-trick-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-paper-airplane-trick-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to make a paper airplane that could do something truly incredible? Well, now you can! With this simple trick, you can make a paper airplane that will defy gravity and keep flying for a surprisingly long time.
Definition of Paper Airplane A paper airplane is a type of toy aircraft, usually made out of paper or cardboard, that is designed to be flown by the force of thrust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>?Find Out the *Savage* Way to Spell This Word and Impress Your Friends!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/find-out-the-savage-way-to-spell-this-word-and-impress-your-friends-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/find-out-the-savage-way-to-spell-this-word-and-impress-your-friends-/</guid>
      <description>Find Out the Savage Way to Spell This Word and Impress Your Friends! Are you looking for a way to impress your friends with your spelling skills? If so, then you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll be discussing the correct way to spell the word “savage” and how you can use it to show off your spelling prowess.
Introduction The word “savage” is defined as “fierce, violent, and uncontrolled” and is often used to describe someone or something that is wild or untamed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Much Blackpink&#39;s &#39;How You Like That&#39; Sold in Its First Week!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-much-blackpink-s-how-you-like-that-sold-in-its-first-week-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-much-blackpink-s-how-you-like-that-sold-in-its-first-week-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is one of the most popular K-Pop girl groups in the world, and their latest single &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; has been an absolute smash hit. In its first week of release, the single sold an incredible amount of copies, and it&amp;rsquo;s a testament to Blackpink&amp;rsquo;s incredible success and popularity. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the sales of &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; in its first week, and how it compares to other artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grandeCan You Believe This? Find Out How to Spell Ariana Grande&#39;s Name Right Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/grandecan-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-ariana-grande-s-name-right-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/grandecan-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-ariana-grande-s-name-right-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ariana Grande is one of the most popular singers and songwriters of the 21st century. From her hit singles to her award-winning albums, Ariana has made a name for herself in the music industry. But there&amp;rsquo;s one thing that has always stumped fans and casual listeners alike: how to spell Ariana Grande&amp;rsquo;s name correctly.
Overview of Ariana Grande Ariana Grande-Butera was born on June 26, 13 in Boca Raton, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Just Did - Get Ready to Be Blown Away!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-get-ready-to-be-blown-away-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-get-ready-to-be-blown-away-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is a South Korean girl group that has taken the world by storm since their debut in 2016. They have become one of the most popular K-pop groups in the world and have achieved immense success in the music industry. Recently, they made a surprise announcement that has left their fans in awe. Read on to find out what they did and why it has made such a big impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Just Did - You&#39;ll Love It!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-you-ll-love-it-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-you-ll-love-it-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is one of the most popular K-pop girl groups in the world. Their music, fashion, and style have been embraced by millions of fans around the world. Recently, Blackpink did something that has taken the world by storm. Read on to learn more about what Blackpink just did and the impact it has had.
Overview of Blackpink Blackpink is a four-member girl group from South Korea. The group consists of members Jisoo, Jennie, Lisa, and Rosé.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Poster Just Dropped the Hottest Song of the Summer - You Won&#39;t Believe What She Did Next!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/lisa-poster-just-dropped-the-hottest-song-of-the-summer-you-won-t-believe-what-she-did-next-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/lisa-poster-just-dropped-the-hottest-song-of-the-summer-you-won-t-believe-what-she-did-next-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This summer, Lisa Poster has taken the music world by storm with her latest single, &amp;ldquo;Can&amp;rsquo;t Stop Now&amp;rdquo;. Not only is the song an instant hit, but Lisa has been taking bold steps to ensure that her music reaches as many people as possible. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the background of Lisa Poster, the reaction to her new song, and what she&amp;rsquo;s been up to since its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Jisoo Just Did - You&#39;ll Love It!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-jisoo-just-did-you-ll-love-it-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-jisoo-just-did-you-ll-love-it-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Jisoo is a South Korean singer and actress, best known as a member of the K-pop girl group BLACKPINK. She is known for her amazing vocals, stunning visuals, and her bubbly personality. Recently, she made a move that has left everyone in awe.
Overview of Jisoo Jisoo is one of the most popular and successful members of BLACKPINK. She has gained a massive fan following over the years, and her fans have been eagerly waiting for her to make her solo debut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Old Dream&#39;s Minecraft World Is!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-old-dream-s-minecraft-world-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-old-dream-s-minecraft-world-is-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Old Dream&amp;rsquo;s Minecraft World Is! Dream is a popular YouTuber and streamer who has been playing Minecraft for years. He has built an incredible world in the game, and it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most impressive creations in the Minecraft community. But what many people don&amp;rsquo;t know is just how old Dream&amp;rsquo;s Minecraft world is!
Introduction Dream is a well-known Minecraft player who has been playing the game since 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Black Pink&#39;s Lisa Just Did - How You Like That!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-black-pink-s-lisa-just-did-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-black-pink-s-lisa-just-did-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Black Pink is one of the most popular K-pop girl groups in the world. The group consists of four members: Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa. Lisa, the group&amp;rsquo;s main dancer and lead rapper, recently made headlines with her latest activity. Read on to find out what Black Pink&amp;rsquo;s Lisa just did!
What Black Pink&amp;rsquo;s Lisa Just Did Recently, Lisa released her first solo single, &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo;. The song quickly became a global hit, reaching number one on the iTunes charts in over 40 countries and topping the Billboard Global Excl.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
