<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Setting Up Your Facebook Account in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-setting-up-your-facebook-account-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-setting-up-your-facebook-account-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking to join the millions of people who use Facebook? Setting up an account is easier than ever before. In this blog post, we will discuss the process of setting up a Facebook account and the benefits of doing so.
Overview of the Process Setting up a Facebook account is a simple process that can be done in a few easy steps. You will need to provide some basic information, such as your name, email address, and birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When This Person Got 1 Million Youtube Views!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-got-1-million-youtube-views-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-got-1-million-youtube-views-/</guid>
      <description>I. Introduction If you’re a content creator on YouTube, you know that getting one million views on a video is a huge accomplishment. But what happens when you actually reach that milestone? Well, one person recently found out when their video got one million views, and the results were amazing!
II. What Happened When the Video Got 1 Million Views When this person’s video got one million views, they were absolutely ecstatic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
