<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>English Grammar on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/english-grammar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English Grammar on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/english-grammar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are You Spellbound? Find Out How to Spell &#39;Appear&#39; Right Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-spellbound-find-out-how-to-spell-appear-right-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-spellbound-find-out-how-to-spell-appear-right-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever feel spellbound when you have to spell a word? Many people find it difficult to remember how to spell the word &amp;ldquo;appear&amp;rdquo;. It’s a tricky word that can be easily misspelled.
In this blog post, we’ll look at the definition of the word “appear” and discuss the reasons for learning how to spell it properly. We’ll also provide some steps to help you spell “appear” correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Struggling to Spell &#39;Epitome&#39;? Find Out the Right Way Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-struggling-to-spell-epitome-find-out-the-right-way-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-struggling-to-spell-epitome-find-out-the-right-way-now-/</guid>
      <description>Are You Struggling to Spell &amp;lsquo;Epitome&amp;rsquo;? Find Out the Right Way Now! Are you struggling to spell the word &amp;rsquo;epitome&amp;rsquo;? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! Many people find it difficult to spell this word correctly. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what the word means and why people find it difficult to spell. We&amp;rsquo;ll also provide some helpful tips and tricks on how to spell &amp;rsquo;epitome&amp;rsquo; correctly.
I. Introduction Do you want to know how to spell &amp;rsquo;epitome&amp;rsquo; correctly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Master the Correct Spelling of &#39;Article&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-master-the-correct-spelling-of-article-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-master-the-correct-spelling-of-article-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you struggling to spell the word &amp;lsquo;article&amp;rsquo;? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! Many people find it difficult to remember the correct spelling for this word, but luckily there is a simple trick that can help you master it. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the definition of &amp;lsquo;article&amp;rsquo; and explain the trick that can help you learn to spell it correctly.
Definition of Article The word &amp;lsquo;article&amp;rsquo; is a noun that refers to a piece of writing on a particular subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Making This Common Spelling Mistake? Find Out the Correct Way to Spell &#39;Slept&#39; Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-making-this-common-spelling-mistake-find-out-the-correct-way-to-spell-slept-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-making-this-common-spelling-mistake-find-out-the-correct-way-to-spell-slept-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Common Spelling Mistakes We all make mistakes when it comes to spelling. It’s easy to misspell words, especially when we’re in a hurry or not paying close attention. One of the most common spelling mistakes is the word ‘slept’. In this blog post, we’ll explain the correct way to spell this word and provide some helpful tips on how to avoid making this mistake in the future.
Explanation of the Correct Way to Spell ‘Slept’ The correct spelling of the word ‘slept’ is ‘slept’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Making This Embarrassing Spelling Mistake with &#39;Optional&#39;? Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-making-this-embarrassing-spelling-mistake-with-optional-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-making-this-embarrassing-spelling-mistake-with-optional-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Are You Making This Embarrassing Spelling Mistake with &amp;lsquo;Optional&amp;rsquo;? Do you know when to use the word “optional”? Are you sure you’re using it correctly? Many people make the embarrassing mistake of misusing “optional” when they should be using “optionally” or vice versa. To help you avoid this common mistake, let’s take a look at what “optional” means, the most common mistakes people make with it, and how to avoid them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Making the Embarrassing Mistake of Spelling &#39;Behave&#39; Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-making-the-embarrassing-mistake-of-spelling-behave-wrong-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-making-the-embarrassing-mistake-of-spelling-behave-wrong-/</guid>
      <description>Are You Making the Embarrassing Mistake of Spelling &amp;lsquo;Behave&amp;rsquo; Wrong? If you’ve ever been embarrassed by misspelling the word “behave”, you’re not alone. This is a common mistake that many people make, and it’s important to understand the difference between the various forms of the word to ensure you’re using it correctly.
I. Introduction “Behave” is an English verb that is used to describe an action or attitude. It’s commonly used in a variety of contexts, and it’s important to understand the differences between the various forms of the word to ensure you’re using it correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
