<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far This Simple Paper Airplane Can Fly!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-simple-paper-airplane-can-fly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-simple-paper-airplane-can-fly-/</guid>
      <description>I. Introduction Have you ever wanted to fly a paper airplane? If so, you’re in for a treat. We recently discovered a paper airplane that can fly an impressive distance, and you won’t believe how far it can go!
II. Design of the Paper Airplane The paper airplane is made from one sheet of 8.5x11 inch paper. It is designed with two wings and a long tail for stability. The wings are curved to create lift and the tail is designed to keep the plane on course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Plane Fly Farther Than Ever Before!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-plane-fly-farther-than-ever-before-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-plane-fly-farther-than-ever-before-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you want to make your paper plane fly farther than ever before? If you do, then this simple trick is just what you need! In this blog post, we will explain how to make your paper plane fly farther than ever before.
Background Information Paper planes have been around for centuries. They are a great way to have fun and pass the time. For many people, paper planes are a beloved childhood pastime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far This Paper Airplane Flies!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-airplane-flies-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-airplane-flies-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper airplanes are a classic childhood pastime, but they can be much more than just a fun way to pass the time. In this post, we will explore the science behind paper airplanes, the benefits of paper airplanes, and some fascinating facts about paper airplane flights.
Overview of Paper Airplanes Paper airplanes are a simple craft that anyone can make. All you need is a piece of paper and a few folds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Incredible Trick Will Make Any Paper Plane Fly Further Than You Ever Thought Possible!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-incredible-trick-will-make-any-paper-plane-fly-further-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-incredible-trick-will-make-any-paper-plane-fly-further-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</guid>
      <description>This Incredible Trick Will Make Any Paper Plane Fly Further Than You Ever Thought Possible! Are you looking for a way to take your paper plane flying skills to the next level? Have you ever wanted to make a paper plane that could fly further than you ever thought possible? Well, you’re in luck! In this blog post, we’ll be discussing an incredible trick that will make any paper plane fly further than you ever thought possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far This Paper Jet Can Fly - See It Fly 100 Feet!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-jet-can-fly-see-it-fly-100-feet-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-jet-can-fly-see-it-fly-100-feet-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Introduction Making a paper jet is a fun and creative activity that can be enjoyed by people of all ages. It is a simple and inexpensive way to explore the principles of aerodynamics and have some fun in the process. In this blog post, we will explore the process of making a paper jet and then demonstrate how far it can fly.
Definition of a Paper Jet A paper jet is a paper airplane that is designed to fly farther and faster than a traditional paper airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far You Can Make Your Paper Airplane Fly!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-you-can-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-you-can-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to make a paper airplane that could fly really far? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! With just a few simple steps, you can make a paper airplane that will fly farther than you ever imagined. Read on to find out how!
Steps to Make a Paper Airplane Making a paper airplane is a simple and fun activity that anyone can do. Here are the basic steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Plane Glider Fly Further Than Ever Before!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-plane-glider-fly-further-than-ever-before-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-plane-glider-fly-further-than-ever-before-/</guid>
      <description>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Plane Glider Fly Further Than Ever Before! Do you ever wish your paper plane glider could fly further? Have you been searching for the perfect trick to make your paper plane soar? Look no further! This simple trick will make your paper plane glider fly further than ever before.
A. Overview of the Simple Trick The trick is to add a tail to your paper plane glider.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
