<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aerodynamics on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/aerodynamics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aerodynamics on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/aerodynamics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>airplaneUnbelievable! This Simple Trick will Make Your Paper Airplane Fly Like a Real Airplane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/airplaneunbelievable-this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-like-a-real-airplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/airplaneunbelievable-this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-like-a-real-airplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Paper Airplanes Paper airplanes are a fun and easy way to explore the world of flight. Making a paper airplane is a great activity for kids and adults alike and can be a great way to pass the time. With just a few simple materials, you can make your paper airplane fly like a real airplane!
The Trick Making a paper airplane fly like a real airplane is easier than you might think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Secret to Making Paper Planes That Fly Farther Than You Ever Imagined!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/discover-the-secret-to-making-paper-planes-that-fly-farther-than-you-ever-imagined-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/discover-the-secret-to-making-paper-planes-that-fly-farther-than-you-ever-imagined-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper planes are an enjoyable and creative way to explore the principles of flight. From the backyard to the science lab, paper planes can be used to explore the effects of air resistance, lift, and thrust. With the right techniques, you can make paper planes that fly farther than you ever imagined!
Definition of Paper Planes A paper plane, or paper aeroplane, is a toy aircraft made out of paper or cardstock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Take Your Paper Aeroplane Flying To The Next Level!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-take-your-paper-aeroplane-flying-to-the-next-level-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-take-your-paper-aeroplane-flying-to-the-next-level-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper aeroplanes are a classic pastime that can provide hours of entertainment. Whether you’re a child or an adult, there’s something special about the simple pleasure of watching a paper aeroplane soar through the air. But did you know that there’s a simple trick that can take your paper aeroplane flying to the next level? In this blog post, we’ll explain the trick and how to master it.
Overview of Paper Aeroplanes Paper aeroplanes are a type of toy aircraft that are typically constructed from a single sheet of paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far This Paper Airplane Flies - Discover the Secret to Making a Long Lasting Plane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-airplane-flies-discover-the-secret-to-making-a-long-lasting-plane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-airplane-flies-discover-the-secret-to-making-a-long-lasting-plane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper airplanes have been a classic pastime for generations of children and adults alike. Not only are they a fun activity, but they also offer a great way to explore the principles of aerodynamics. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the secrets to making a paper airplane that can fly for a surprisingly long distance.
What is a Paper Airplane? A paper airplane is a type of plane made out of a single sheet of paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>farThis Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Airplane Fly Farther Than You Ever Thought Possible!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/farthis-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/farthis-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper airplanes are a classic pastime for children and adults alike. They are simple to make, fun to fly, and can provide hours of entertainment. But what if you could make your paper airplane fly farther than ever before? Well, with this simple trick, you can!
Definition of a Paper Airplane A paper airplane is a toy aircraft made from paper or paperboard. It is usually constructed by folding a piece of paper or paperboard into a triangular shape and then launching it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fly betterThis Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Aeroplane Soar Like Never Before!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/fly-betterthis-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-aeroplane-soar-like-never-before-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/fly-betterthis-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-aeroplane-soar-like-never-before-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A paper aeroplane is a classic childhood pastime that has been enjoyed by generations. It’s a simple yet effective way to entertain yourself, and with a little bit of practice and know-how, you can make your paper aeroplane soar higher than ever before!
What is a paper aeroplane? A paper aeroplane is a type of toy aircraft made from a sheet of paper or card, usually with two or more folds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>airplaneThis Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Airplane Fly Faster Than a Real Airplane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/airplanethis-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-faster-than-a-real-airplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/airplanethis-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-faster-than-a-real-airplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Paper Airplanes Paper airplanes are a fun and easy way to explore the science of flight. With just a few simple materials, you can make your own paper airplane and watch it soar through the air. But what if you could make your paper airplane fly faster than a real airplane? Sounds impossible, right? Well, it’s not! With this simple trick, you can make your paper airplane fly faster than a real airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
