<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hobbies on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/hobbies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hobbies on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/hobbies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable! You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy it is to Make a Paper Airplane with These Step-by-Step Instructions!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/unbelievable-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-a-paper-airplane-with-these-step-by-step-instructions-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/unbelievable-you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-a-paper-airplane-with-these-step-by-step-instructions-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Making a paper airplane is a fun and easy activity that anyone can do! It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to pass the time, and it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to get creative. Plus, it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to learn about aerodynamics and engineering. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the basics of making a paper airplane, and provide step-by-step instructions so you can make your own.
Definition of a Paper Airplane A paper airplane is a simple aircraft made from a piece of paper or cardstock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make You a Paper Plane Expert in Just 5 Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-a-paper-plane-expert-in-just-5-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-a-paper-plane-expert-in-just-5-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper planes are one of the most beloved childhood activities, but mastering the skill of making them can be tricky. Even adults can struggle to make a good paper plane. But with this simple trick, you can become a paper plane expert in just minutes!
Background Information Paper planes have been around for centuries, but the modern paper plane was developed in the early 100s. Since then, paper planes have become a staple in the childhood game of make-believe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Launching Airplanes in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-launching-airplanes-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-launching-airplanes-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a budding aviator looking to launch your first airplane? Or perhaps you’ve been flying for years and want to brush up on the basics? Either way, we’ve got you covered! There’s no need to be intimidated by the prospect of launching an airplane. With the right knowledge and a few simple tricks, anyone can become a pro in no time.
Step-by-Step Guide to Launching an Airplane Make sure the plane is ready for flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make You a Paper Airplane Master in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-a-paper-airplane-master-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-a-paper-airplane-master-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>This Simple Trick Will Make You a Paper Airplane Master in No Time! Paper airplanes are a classic childhood pastime that still bring joy to people of all ages. Whether you’re looking for a fun activity to do with your kids or just want to take a break from the hustle and bustle of everyday life, learning how to make paper airplanes is a great way to do it. With a few simple steps, you can become a paper airplane master in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Launching Paper Airplanes That Fly Further Than You Ever Imagined!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-launching-paper-airplanes-that-fly-further-than-you-ever-imagined-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-launching-paper-airplanes-that-fly-further-than-you-ever-imagined-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper airplanes are a fun and easy way to get kids outside and away from screens. Not only do they provide a great source of entertainment, but they can also help children learn about aerodynamics and physics. In this blog post, we will discuss the benefits of launching paper airplanes, as well as a simple trick that will have you launching paper airplanes that fly further than you ever imagined!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
