<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Trivia on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/trivia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trivia on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/trivia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can You Believe This? Find Out How to Spell 8 and Amaze Your Friends!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-8-and-amaze-your-friends-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-believe-this-find-out-how-to-spell-8-and-amaze-your-friends-/</guid>
      <description>Can You Believe This? Find Out How to Spell 8 and Amaze Your Friends! Have you ever been in a situation where you were asked to spell the number 8 but had no idea how to do it? It can be a tricky one to remember! But don’t worry, we’ll show you how to spell 8 and wow your friends with your newfound knowledge.
Introduction Spelling is an important skill to have, and understanding how to spell the number 8 is no exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Ace This Quiz and Spell &#39;Tournament&#39; Correctly?</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-ace-this-quiz-and-spell-tournament-correctly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-ace-this-quiz-and-spell-tournament-correctly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you ready to test your spelling skills? We’re hosting a tournament to see who can spell the word “tournament” correctly! If you think you have what it takes, then read on to learn more about the rules and regulations of the tournament and the prizes you can win.
Quiz Rules and Regulations The quiz will be open to anyone who wishes to participate. The quiz will consist of 10 questions related to spelling and grammar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know How to Spell This Word? You&#39;ll Be Surprised by the Answer!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/do-you-know-how-to-spell-this-word-you-ll-be-surprised-by-the-answer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/do-you-know-how-to-spell-this-word-you-ll-be-surprised-by-the-answer-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you know how to spell this word? Many people have difficulty with this word and are often surprised by the correct spelling. In this article, we will explore the origin, etymology, and common misconceptions about the word.
Definition of the Word The word in question is &amp;ldquo;surreptitious&amp;rdquo;. It is an adjective that means done, made, or acquired by stealth or in a clandestine manner.
Purpose of the Article The purpose of this article is to explain the origin and etymology of the word &amp;ldquo;surreptitious&amp;rdquo; as well as to dispel any common misconceptions about its spelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Believe This: 88 Has Stumped Even the Best Spellers!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-believe-this-88-has-stumped-even-the-best-spellers-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/can-you-believe-this-88-has-stumped-even-the-best-spellers-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that spelling can be a challenge for many people. But, recently, a new challenge has emerged that has even stumped the best spellers: 88. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the difficulty of spelling 88, and the implications of this challenge.
Background Information 88 is a number that has been used in many contexts. It&amp;rsquo;s been used as a code for the letter &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; in the military and in the aviation industry, and it&amp;rsquo;s been used to represent the number of keys on a piano.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
