<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable: Installing Postgresql on Mac Is Easier Than You Think!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/unbelievable-installing-postgresql-on-mac-is-easier-than-you-think-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/unbelievable-installing-postgresql-on-mac-is-easier-than-you-think-/</guid>
      <description>Unbelievable: Installing Postgresql on Mac Is Easier Than You Think! Are you looking for a powerful open-source relational database system for your Mac? PostgreSQL is a great choice and the good news is that installing it is easier than you think! In this blog post, we’ll discuss what PostgreSQL is, the benefits of using it, and how to install it on your Mac.
I. Introduction PostgreSQL is a powerful object-relational database system that is used by many businesses and organizations around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Setting Up Your Facebook Account in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-setting-up-your-facebook-account-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-setting-up-your-facebook-account-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking to join the millions of people who use Facebook? Setting up an account is easier than ever before. In this blog post, we will discuss the process of setting up a Facebook account and the benefits of doing so.
Overview of the Process Setting up a Facebook account is a simple process that can be done in a few easy steps. You will need to provide some basic information, such as your name, email address, and birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy it is to Get Google Play on Your Amazon Fire 7!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-get-google-play-on-your-amazon-fire-7-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-get-google-play-on-your-amazon-fire-7-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Easy it is to Get Google Play on Your Amazon Fire 7! Are you an Amazon Fire 7 user looking to get the most out of your device? If so, you’re in luck – it’s incredibly easy to add Google Play to your tablet. With Google Play, you can access a wide selection of apps, games, and other content. Keep reading to learn more about the benefits of adding Google Play to your Amazon Fire 7 and to get step-by-step instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Setting Up a New Google Account in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-setting-up-a-new-google-account-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-setting-up-a-new-google-account-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking to set up a new Google Account? It&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the simple steps to get you up and running in no time.
Steps to Setting Up a Google Account Go to the Google homepage and click the &amp;ldquo;Sign In&amp;rdquo; button in the top right corner. Click the &amp;ldquo;Create Account&amp;rdquo; button. Enter your name, email address, and a password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Show You How to Create a Valid Email Address Instantly!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-show-you-how-to-create-a-valid-email-address-instantly-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-show-you-how-to-create-a-valid-email-address-instantly-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a quick and easy way to create a valid email address? If so, you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll walk you through the simple steps of creating a valid email address in no time.
Overview of Valid Email Addresses A valid email address is an email address that is correctly formatted and can be used to send and receive emails. It typically consists of a username and a domain name, such as “[username]@[domain].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far This Paper Jet Can Fly - See It Fly 100 Feet!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-jet-can-fly-see-it-fly-100-feet-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-paper-jet-can-fly-see-it-fly-100-feet-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Introduction Making a paper jet is a fun and creative activity that can be enjoyed by people of all ages. It is a simple and inexpensive way to explore the principles of aerodynamics and have some fun in the process. In this blog post, we will explore the process of making a paper jet and then demonstrate how far it can fly.
Definition of a Paper Jet A paper jet is a paper airplane that is designed to fly farther and faster than a traditional paper airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Trick Will Help You Double the Battery Life of Your Redmi Phone!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-help-you-double-the-battery-life-of-your-redmi-phone-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-one-trick-will-help-you-double-the-battery-life-of-your-redmi-phone-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you own a Redmi phone and want to get more out of its battery life? If so, then you’re in luck! We’ve got a great trick that can help you double the battery life of your Redmi phone. Read on to learn more about the benefits of this trick and how to implement it.
Benefits of this Trick This trick is great because it can help you get more out of your Redmi phone’s battery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
