<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Memory&#34; on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/memory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memory&#34; on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/memory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>tsThis Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Spell &#39;Triplets&#39; Like a Pro!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/tsthis-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-spell-triplets-like-a-pro-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/tsthis-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-spell-triplets-like-a-pro-/</guid>
      <description>This Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Spell &amp;lsquo;Triplets&amp;rsquo; Like a Pro! We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there – you need to write the word &amp;rsquo;triplets&amp;rsquo; but you just can&amp;rsquo;t spell it! It can be frustrating, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry – we&amp;rsquo;ve got the perfect solution for you. This simple trick will help you instantly spell &amp;rsquo;triplets&amp;rsquo; like a pro!
Introduction Let&amp;rsquo;s start by defining what a triplet is. A triplet is a group of three siblings born at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Remember How to Spell &#39;Luigi&#39; - You&#39;ll Be Surprised!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-remember-how-to-spell-luigi-you-ll-be-surprised-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-remember-how-to-spell-luigi-you-ll-be-surprised-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you have trouble remembering how to spell the name of everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite Nintendo character, Luigi? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many people struggle with this common problem, but luckily, there&amp;rsquo;s a simple trick you can use to help you remember how to spell Luigi&amp;rsquo;s name correctly.
The Trick The trick is to break the name up into two parts: &amp;ldquo;Lu&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;igi.&amp;rdquo; To remember how to spell &amp;ldquo;Lu,&amp;rdquo; think of the phrase &amp;ldquo;Lucky you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a long wordUnbelievable Trick to Easily Spell Any Word No Matter How Long It Is!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/a-long-wordunbelievable-trick-to-easily-spell-any-word-no-matter-how-long-it-is-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/a-long-wordunbelievable-trick-to-easily-spell-any-word-no-matter-how-long-it-is-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Introduction to Spelling Long Words Do you ever find yourself struggling to spell long words? It can be an intimidating task to tackle, but with a few simple tricks, you can easily master any long word. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the definition of a long word and provide an overview of the trick. We&amp;rsquo;ll then go into detail about the steps to easily spell any long word, as well as the best ways to practice the trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Stumped? Find Out the Amazingly Simple Trick to Spell &#39;Wild&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-stumped-find-out-the-amazingly-simple-trick-to-spell-wild-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/are-you-stumped-find-out-the-amazingly-simple-trick-to-spell-wild-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever find yourself stumped on how to spell the word &amp;lsquo;wild&amp;rsquo;? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! It can be difficult to remember the correct spelling of this word, but luckily there&amp;rsquo;s an amazingly simple trick that can help you out. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the definition of &amp;lsquo;wild&amp;rsquo;, provide an overview of the trick, and then discuss each step of the trick in detail.
The Trick The trick to spelling &amp;lsquo;wild&amp;rsquo; is surprisingly simple: just remember the phrase &amp;ldquo;WILD is a party!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wordsThis Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Spell Any Long Word!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/wordsthis-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-spell-any-long-word-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/wordsthis-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-spell-any-long-word-/</guid>
      <description>This Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Spell Any Long Word! Do you ever find yourself struggling to spell long words? Don’t worry, you’re not alone. Long words can be difficult to spell, but with a few simple tricks, you can learn to spell them quickly and easily.
Definition of Long Words Long words are words that have more than one syllable and are usually composed of several smaller words. Examples of long words include “antidisestablishmentarianism”, “supercalifragilisticexpialidocious”, and “pseudopseudohypoparathyroidism”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
