<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aviation on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/aviation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aviation on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/aviation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try to Make an Airplane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-to-make-an-airplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-to-make-an-airplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to make an airplane? It can seem like a daunting task, but with a little bit of knowledge and some hard work, it is possible. In this blog post, we will explore the process of making an airplane and the unexpected challenges and outcomes that come along with it.
Background Information Making an airplane is no easy feat. It requires knowledge of aeronautical engineering and a deep understanding of the physics of flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Make the World&#39;s Best Airplane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-make-the-world-s-best-airplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-make-the-world-s-best-airplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered what it would be like to fly in the world&amp;rsquo;s best airplane? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re about to find out! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the design, performance, and benefits of the world&amp;rsquo;s best airplane. Read on to learn more about this amazing aircraft!
Overview of the World&amp;rsquo;s Best Airplane The world&amp;rsquo;s best airplane is a state-of-the-art aircraft that has been designed with the latest technology and materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make Your Own Airplane!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-your-own-airplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-your-own-airplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever dreamed of flying your own airplane? It may seem like a daunting task, but making your own airplane is actually quite achievable. With the right materials and a bit of know-how, you can have your own plane ready for takeoff in no time.
Benefits of Making Your Own Airplane Building your own airplane has a number of benefits. First and foremost, you can save a lot of money.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
