<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Toys and Games on Marintarisa</title>
    <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/toys-and-games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toys and Games on Marintarisa</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marintarisa.github.io/tags/toys-and-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Make This Paper Plane That Does Tricks!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-make-this-paper-plane-that-does-tricks-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-make-this-paper-plane-that-does-tricks-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You Make This Paper Plane That Does Tricks! Have you ever wanted to make a paper plane that can do tricks? If so, you’re in luck! This article will provide an overview of paper plane tricks, the benefits of making a plane that does tricks, and a step-by-step guide on how to make the plane.
Overview of Paper Plane Tricks Paper plane tricks are a fun way to entertain yourself and your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable! This Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Airplane Fly Farther Than You Ever Imagined!</title>
      <link>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-imagined-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marintarisa.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-imagined-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper airplanes are a classic childhood activity, and with the right technique, you can make your paper airplane fly farther than you ever imagined! This simple trick will help you to make your paper airplane soar to new heights.
What is a Paper Airplane? A paper airplane is a toy aircraft, usually made out of paper, that is designed to be flown in the air. Paper airplanes are usually made by folding a sheet of paper into a symmetrical shape, and then adding weight to the nose to make it fly better.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
